(Leonard:)Why?
(Sheldon:)The learning opportunities
would be abundant.
(Sheldon:)Additionally...
(Sheldon:)...I like having my belly scratched.
- Hey, Penny. How was work?
- Great.
(Penny:)I hope I'm a waitress at
the Cheesecake Factory for my whole life.
(Sheldon:)Was that sarcasm?
(Sheldon:)No.
(Sheldon:)Yes.
- Was that sarcasm?
- Stop it.
Penny?
(Sheldon:)- You appear to have a package here.
- Oh, thanks.
It must be the beret I ordered.
(Penny:)A couple of months ago.
It was back-ordered.
(Sheldon:)Did you know the beret
is an example...
...of a piece of women's fashion
adapted from male military uniforms?
(Sheldon:)Another fascinating example
is the epaulet.
(Leonard:)He's not lying.
He does find that fascinating.
Okay, look, whatever.
(Penny:)It's not like I'm running up and down
the streets buying berets.
I bought one a month ago
when it was back-ordered. It finally arrived.